everlend.app
everlend.app
is a secure financial protocol for
— это безопасный финансовый протокол для
earning passive income on personal
получения пассивного дохода от личных
crypto savings and for lending created
сбережений в криптовалюте и для кредитования,
everlend has been developed on the
созданный командой svoi.dev.
incentivize liquidity providers and
стимулировать поставщиков ликвидности и
lenders let's take a closer look at how
кредиторов давайте подробнее рассмотрим, как
this financial protocol works
работает этот финансовый протокол
lenders transfer their digital assets to
кредиторы переводят свои цифровые активы
the liquidity pool other everlend.app
в пул ликвидности другие
users can then borrow from this pool
пользователи everlend.app могут затем брать займы из этого пула
interest rates on loans and deposits are
процентные ставки по кредитам и депозитам
floating they're constantly adjusted by
плавающие они постоянно корректируются
algorithmic methods that take into
алгоритмические методы, которые
account current supply and demand so how
учитывают текущее предложение и спрос, поэтому, как
do you get a loan
вы получаете кредит,
the platform lends usdt stablecoins
платформа предоставляет usdt стабильные монеты
against w weather the wrapped version of
против w, завернутая версия
evercoins and vice versa loans can be
evercoins и наоборот, кредиты могут быть
returned at any time
возвращены в любое время,
the key thing to remember is that if the
главное помнить, что если
value of the collateral falls to the
значение  залога падает до
amount to be given back
суммы, подлежащей возврату,
a margin call will be triggered and the
инициируется маржин-колл, и
deal will automatically close in this
сделка  автоматически закроется, в этом
case the cl later on will be forcibly
случае cl позже будет принудительно
liquidated by the platform
ликвидирован платформой,
so let's take a look at the profitable
поэтому давайте взглянем на прибыльные
strategies on everland.app
стратегии на everland.app,
using evelend you can earn on both
используя evelend, вы можете зарабатывать как на
increases and decreases in the value of
увеличении, так и на уменьшении стоимости
wever please remember all of these
wever, пожалуйста, помните все это
strategies can be risky and i am not a
стратегии могут быть рискованными, и я не являюсь
financial advisor so to be able to
финансовым консультантом, поэтому, чтобы получить
potentially profit from the growth of
потенциальную прибыль от
the w ever price it's possible to use
роста любой цены, можно
the tokens and as collateral and borrow
использовать токены и в качестве залога и брать
stable coins you can also buy more w
стабильные монеты, вы также можете покупать
ever with these stable coins to profit
больше с этими стабильными монетами.  чтобы получить прибыль
from a decrease in price just use usdt
от снижения цены, просто используйте доллары США в
as collateral and borrow weather to sell
качестве залога и займите погоду, чтобы
the funds you can rebuy them later at a
продать средства, вы можете выкупить их позже по более
lower price and get the currency back
низкой цене и получить валюту обратно,
earning on the price difference it's
заработав на разнице в цене,
possible to withdraw your funds at any
вы можете снять свои средства в любое
time
время
and thanks to the high level of
и благодаря  высокий уровень
transaction security user friendly
безопасности транзакций удобный
interface and low fees this young and
интерфейс и низкие комиссии у этого молодого и
promising lending service has every
перспективного кредитного сервиса есть все
chance of becoming one of the leaders in
шансы стать одним из
the cryptocurrency lending market
лидеров крипторынка  рынок срочного кредитования